All right. Before I bring up Dex, I
gotta say I met James. And James Yeah.
Can you stand up real fast? James told
me this morning that he is going We
can't see the QR code. You got to hit it
up. He's going to be having dinner
tonight and everybody's invited. So, if
you want to go, just scan that QR code
real fast and go hang out with James.
That's awesome. And that's what we're
going for here. That is great.
>> Yeah, you rock. Yeah, that's I like it.
I like it, too. Okay, so I'm gonna bring
up Dex. Uh earlier somebody said we need
to have a mustache competition. I don't
think that's going to happen, but I will
say that he gave us 200 slides that he's
about to present.
>> Whoa, whoa. 158.
>> 158. We're going to keep him honest on
the timing. All right, so let it start
nowing everybody.
>> Let's do it. What's up everybody?
>> Dex.
>> Yeah.
>> Uh I am Dex. Uh this is a talk with a
very long title that I'm not going to
read because we're on the clock now. Uh
I have been talking about coding agents
for quite a while. Basically since like
August um we did a long talk in
November. Um there's this methodology
that we've been talking about a lot uh
called research plan implement. Um a lot
of up votes on hackernews. There's
probably 10,000 people who have gone to
our open source and grabbed our prompts
and are using them internally from small
startups up to the enterprise. Um it all
started with this guy. Um this guy has
anyone seen this talk?
>> Yes. Okay. So Eigor went in and he said
like okay cool we're using a lot of
tokens we're spending a lot of money to
get AI developer productivity. But what
he found was that it actually tends to
lead to a lot of rework. Like you are
shipping 50% more but half of that is
just cleaning up the slop from last
week. And the other thing they found,
and these are last year's numbers, so
this does not account for opus 4.5. So I
would I would inflate this a little bit,
but like it's great for low complexity
green field tasks, not great for
high complexity brownfield tasks. Um,
and so I could give you a talk about RPI
and why it's great. Uh, but that would
be boring. And there's other talks, so
if you haven't seen them, go watch them.
It'll give more context. But, uh, I'm
going to tell you everything we got
wrong about RPI today. Um, we thought we
had this AI thing thing figured out. I,
uh, am am, uh, humble enough to admit
when I was wrong. Uh, so we got a couple
things wrong. Uh, one thing that's very
relevant if you've been on Twitter today
is, uh, I don't think it's okay to not
read the code. Uh, I also don't think
you should read really long plan files.
Uh, those two are related. Uh, and no,
Cloud should not be allowed to if you if
you writing production code that is used
by users and you're going to get patient
3 a.m. if it's broken. Uh, no slop. This
is the year 2026. No more slop. So,
we're all on this journey. We're all
figuring this out. We all are wrong all
the time. We did get get a couple things
right. Uh there is no magic prompt. Uh
do not outsource the thinking. You the
engineer are an important part of this
process and seek leverage. There's a lot
of code being written. Find ways to make
sure it's correct without having to read
all of it and resteer after the fact. Um
so, lots of people I'm sure have heard
of research plan implement. Has anyone
actually run this claude command?
Research codebase? Okay, cool. Leave
your hand up if you've run it like this.
Tell me how this system works. Has
anyone run it like this of like, "Hey, I
want to build this thing. Go do the
research."
Okay. Um or maybe go fetch a ticket or
something. What about the create plan uh
prompt? Okay. Couple hands. Uh how many
of you run it like that? Hey, we got to
go build this thing. Yes. Has anyone run
it like this? Work back and forth with
me starting with your open questions and
outline before writing the plan. Okay.
Some of you found out about the magic
words. A lot of people didn't though. Uh
we'll get into why that's a problem. Um
so since October we've basically worked
with thousands of engineers from tiny
startups all the way up to Fortune 500s.
Um and we would find over and over again
we would give these tools to an expert
uh and they would get great results.
They would go sit and talk to Cloud for
70 hours a week and they would start
shipping like crazy. Uh and then they
would go give it to their team and the
results were not always so good. Um and
so people weren't getting good results.
And so we got in the trenches with our
users and we went to go figure out what
was going wrong. And the first thing
that was going wrong was people were not
getting good research. Um, so we talked
about this in November. This is uh one
of the only slides I'm reusing, but you
would pick a zone of your codebase. You
would say, "We're going to build
something over here." And then you would
launch it a coding agent session to go
send these sub agents through these deep
vertical slices through the codebase for
just the context, compressed context
about what is the thing we're about to
go build, right? And we said keep things
objective, discourage opinions, don't
actually put any implementation details
in there. You just want to compress the
truth. What is true about how the code
works today? And a skilled engineer was
really good at taking, okay, here's my
ticket. Let me write some questions that
will cause the model to go touch all the
parts of the codebase that matter. So if
it was, you know, add a new endpoint to
reticulate splines across tenants. We
would say something like, okay, tell me
how endpoint endpoints work and trace
the logic flow for everything that
touches splines and go find the workers
that do all the reticulation. Uh, so if
this is your ticket, a lot of people
would run it like this. they would just
say, "Hey, research codebase. Here's
what I'm building." Um, and the problem
is that good research is all facts. But
if you tell the model what you're
building, then you get opinions. And we
don't, we'll get into why the model
shouldn't have opinions later. Comes
back to this thing that Jake from
Netflix came up with, which is do not
outsource the thinking. Um, the other
thing that wasn't working is people were
getting not great plans. Um, and
basically there were these steps built
into this planning prompt uh that was
this single giant like monolithic thing
with 85 or more instructions. And it had
these steps in it of like cool present
design options to the user uh get
feedback on the structure uh before you
actually go write the plan. And so a
good planning session would look
something like you know you have your
claude system tools and your prompt and
then you say hey create plan loads the
skill looks at your ticket loads your
research doc launches a bunch of sub
aents to go find a bunch of things that
are true about the codebase just
confirms some stuff that wasn't maybe in
the research. This is all one big
context window by the way. Usually I'll
use these columns to mean separate
context windows, but today this is all
one session. I just slides are sideways,
so I had to put them on next to each
other. Um, but the agent would come and
ask questions. So, okay, here's our
options for question one. User would
pick an option. User would pick an
option. And then eventually it would
say, cool, here's the order we're going
to do the things. Um, what do you think?
And the user could say, well, we need to
add a testing step up front, and I want
to swap phases three and four. Assistant
would give the new outline of the
phases. then the user would approve it
and only then would we write our plan
file. Um complex process of aligning
with the user on what was what was going
to be built. Um but for about 50% of
people maybe more if you didn't prompt
it with this work back and forth with me
or Opus was just feeling dumb for that
that particular hour of the day. Um it
would just take the stuff and it would
just immediately go and write the plan
out. And so you would get this and it
would be like cool. I wrote the plan,
didn't ask me any questions, made all
the decisions for me. Yikes. So we gave
the tools to people and some people got
good results and some people didn't. And
we dug in and we were like, "What's the
difference?" Uh, and people would
literally say this to me like, "Well,
you have to say the magic words." And I
found myself in workshops full of
enterprise engineers saying, "Well,
guys, guys, guys, yeah, here's the
software, but don't forget to say the
magic words." It was, quite frankly, it
was embarrassing. But if you said this,
work back and forth with me starting
with your open questions and outline
before writing the plan. Then the agent
would ask you the questions. And this
isn't the user's fault. If you built a
tool that requires hours and hours of
training and reps to get like good
results from, go fix the tool. And so
I'll talk about how we did that. Um, but
why these steps were getting skipped,
the one of the big takeaways I'll give
you today is like you have an
instruction budget. Uh, my co-founder
Kyle is somewhere over here. he wrote
this really good blog post in December
or November I guess technically um that
basically cited this archive paper which
again this is from last year so the
number is probably a little bit higher
now but that frontier LMS could only
follow about 150 to 200 instructions
with like good consistency anything more
than that and it's kind of half
attending to all of them and you're
rolling the dice so if you have a prompt
with 85 instructions and your cloud MD
and your system prompt and your tools
and your MCP
um yeah you're not likely to get full
adherence to the workflow. So, more on
how we fix this later. The other thing
that I think um really wasn't working
for people was like we advocated for
reading the plans that were output. This
is me on stage in November telling
people you have to read the plan
otherwise it won't work. Um some people
even would PR their plans and code
review them together. But a thousand
line plan tends to be about a thousand
lines of code within 10% or so. And
plans can have surprises. So you would
go and you would review the plan and
then you would go write the code and it
would be different. And so you're
telling you're asking one of your
co-workers like, "Okay, go spend an hour
reading this and tell me what's wrong
with it." And then you would go
implement it. It would be different.
They have to go read the code again and
see what the surprises were and what
changed. Um, and so this isn't leverage.
Leverage is about like do less work to
get more output. So the new advice, uh,
don't read the plans. Please read the
code. Uh, just because it's it's the
same amount of work and like look for
leverage elsewhere. And I'll talk about
how we found better leverage. Um, and
you may say, "Hey, Dex, in August you
said don't read the code." You said the
plans are enough. Just don't just just
go just ship and let Cloud do its thing.
I was wrong. I am humble enough to admit
when I was wrong. Uh, this is actually a
very big conversation right now. Please
please read the code. We tried not
reading the code for like six months.
Uh, it did not end well. We had to rip
out and replace large parts of that
system. Um, and you may say, "Hey, Dex,
but other people don't read the code."
Beads, 300,000 lines and counting. Uh,
no one's read that code allegedly. Uh,
OpenClaw Pete's like, "Okay, you know, I
know the structure and the pieces and
how they fit together, but I don't read
every line of every PR. Um, these are
OSS projects. They don't charge money.
They are very very cool projects. I am
humbled, deeply humbled by the
accomplishments of the maintainers and
the stakes are still high. Like if you
break openclaw, a lot of people are
going to be upset but they are different
than if you're say working in a
regulated industry shipping production
SAS code. Um so if you have people who
depend on your code, please I'm begging
you please read it. Please read it. We
have a profession to uphold. 2026 is
supposed to be the year of no more slop.
Uh, literally everyone is talking about
the difference between slop and craft.
Uh, this is why I'm a little mid on
agent swarms and the whole gas town
thing because you still need to be able
to ensure quality and like going 10
times faster doesn't matter if you're
going to throw it all away in 6 months.
So, shoot for 2 to 3x. That's actually
another talk of like how you measure
this and how you actually get there and
maintain like a near human level of
quality. Um, but I'll talk about the
goals and like what you should think
about if you want to get there is you
should have high leverage planning. you
should not outsource the thinking, read
and own the code and ideally we will
avoid uh magic words. So uh we got
better research, we got better plans, we
got better leverage. I'm going to talk
about each of those um as far as like in
general what we and like in specifically
what we did and also some general
concepts as you're building workflows
and systems around coding agents what
you can do. So we talked about a skilled
this is the least exciting one but
talked about how a skilled engineer
could detangle the ticket to the
questions to the research uh and then
the research would be very objective. Um
basically we just hide the ticket from
the context window that's doing research
and we do it deterministically. So
basically you have one context window to
generate questions and then a fresh
context window with no knowledge of what
we're building to go make your research
doc. Um this is pretty trivial if you're
familiar with the concept of query
planning. Um it's similar in concept but
for you know LMS reading through code
bases. Um so I've been hacking on agents
for a while and before we did the coding
agent stuff I wrote this paper called 12
factor agents which was uh allegedly the
first time anyone was like talking a lot
about context engineering. Uh there's
two ways to read context engineering and
most people jumped in. Is anyone
building like rag pipelines? Is it raise
your hand if you built a rag pipeline?
Okay. Some people are feeling uh not
like not raising their hands today. Um,
but it's like, okay, put more
information. You put too much
information in, the model can't make
sense of it. I actually think the more
interesting read of context engineering
is like better instructions and simpler
tasks and smaller context windows. Of
course, we all know Jeff now. I don't
have to introduce him anymore. I used to
have to I used to have to tell people
who Jeff was when I was talking. Um, we
talked about this like context window
thing as the idea of the dumb zone,
which is, you know, you have about
168,000 tokens and 200,000, but some of
them are reserved for output. you have
various things that they're for and
around like 40% on average depending on
what you're doing and how much of your
context is user messages versus files
and all of this stuff you hit this point
where you have degrading results and
obviously sometimes you can get still
get good enough for you results at 60%
but the less of the context window you
use the better results you will get. Um
our friends at data bricks were just
talking about you have too many MCPs the
whole context window is full of
instructions about how to use a bunch of
tools that you don't care about and then
by the time you're writing code the
model is like not good at following your
instructions. So you're not just giving
the model too much information, you're
also probably giving it too many
instructions.
And so the idea of what we were doing
was this thing like makes a lot of
sense. Use prompts for control flow.
This is a customer support example, but
you know, if it's a complaint, go do
this. If it's product feedback, go do
this. If it's a billing issue, go do
this. Um, and what you can do instead is
you can instead of using prompts for
control flow, you can kind of classify
the input and then feed it to a series
of smaller, more focused prompts where
there are far fewer instructions and far
fewer actions to choose from. I'm sure
many of us have already done things like
this to improve the performance of
pipelines. Um, so this was a single mega
prompt with 85 instructions. Um, and if
you did it right, you would go through
all these different steps. All these
different phases were part of that. And
if any of the instructions didn't get
followed, you would skip the things that
made this really high leverage. Um, so
we split it across several prompts and
so like before it was research, plan,
implement. Now it's questions, research,
design, structure, plan, work,
implement, PR. We're actually not going
to have time to talk about the implement
side of the thing today, but um, we
split up the planning into a design
discussion and outline and a plan. And
before it was 85 instructions, now
they're all less than 40, which is
really exciting. And I think some of
them could actually be even smaller.
We're still iterating on them. The
lesson is don't use prompts for control
flow if you can use control flow for
control flow. Like the if statement is
really really powerful and LM are really
good at classifying things. This is not
just true for coding agents. This is any
AI LLM based system you're building. Um
and it's really funny because we were
writing all this stuff and we got on
stage we said like full fat agents don't
work. Don't just call tools in a loop.
Do context engineering and build
workflows and graphs and micro agents.
We told everybody don't do this. And
then we turned around in August and
we're like all right but this cloud code
thing is pretty good. And we turned
around and we wrote this giant
monolithic prompt. So, we figured it was
time to actually go drink our own
Kool-Aid. Um, mind your instruction
budget.
How do we get better leverage? So, we
split things up to get better
instruction following, right? These
three different phases. But we also got
more leverage. I'm going to talk about
why. Because even if the plan is a
thousand lines and the code is 1,000
lines, your design discussion might only
be 200 lines. And you get a lot of
opportunities to resteer in that moment.
And so, what this looks like is
basically where are we going? What does
the final solution look like? And it
has, you know, the current state, the
desired end state, it has the patterns
to follow. How many of you ever like
sent off a coding agent and it like
found the wrong way to do a thing in
your codebase and it followed the bad
patterns? Yes. Right. This is your
chance to go read all the patterns it
found that it thinks are relevant and be
like, "Nope, that's not how we do atomic
SQL updates. That's some engineer that
doesn't work here anymore and it's crazy
and everyone hates it. Go find the way
we do it over there." Um, it'll keep
track of resolved design decisions that
we've made. It will ask open questions.
This is sort of like taking cloud code
plan mode and the ask user question tool
and just brain dumping it all to a
single document that you can interact
with is like moldable and flexible. Um
Matt PCO has this idea, he calls it the
design concept and it's this idea of
like the thing that is locked up in this
context window that is the shared
understanding between you and the agent
of what's being built and how. Uh so we
put in a 200line markdown artifact. Um,
and so we now have human agent
alignment. And the idea here is like
you're forcing the agent to brain dump
out all the things it found, all the
things it wants to do, all the things it
thinks you want, and ask you questions
about things it doesn't know. So you can
do brain surgery on the agent before you
proceed downstream. And it's all about
do not outsource the thinking. You want
to give the agent every single
opportunity to show you what it's wrong
about before you go write 2,000 lines of
code. So uh, 200 lines instead of a,000,
a little bit more leverage. We also get
better leverage from the outline. So if
design is like where are we going the
structure outline is how do we get there
or if you're an engineer who is
miserable because of sitting in meetings
all day there's the like architecture
review and then there's the sprint
planning meeting what are we going to
build and then how do we break it down
into tasks and so we take our design and
we take it to ticket and the research we
build up a new context window and we
create the structure outline and this is
basically highle overview of the phases
not the exact code we're going to write
but just kind of what it's going to look
like what order we're going do the
changes in and how we're going to test
it along the way. Now, I don't actually
test in between every phase, everything
I'm building, but if it's sensitive or
if it's hard or if it's complex, I want
to be able to catch it before it goes
and writes all the code. I want to make
sure each two, three, 400 line block is
correct. Um, and these docs mean lighter
reviews. Instead of reviewing the plan,
this is two things for the same feature.
Plan, eight pages, structure outline,
two-ish pages, much shorter. Um, I like
to think of this, has anyone ever
written a C header file, ah file? Yeah.
Okay, so if the plan is the
implementation, the outline is the C
header files. Just here's the signatures
and the new types that we're changing
enough again for you to see what the
agent is thinking and correct it if it's
wrong. Um, and the reason why we do this
is despite like every single model and
trying to prompt this out and eval the
hell out of this, we cannot get models
to stop writing horizontal plans or it
like this is the best way to fix their
need to write horizontal plans. And when
I say horizontal plans, I basically mean
you start with models love to like we're
going to do all the database and then
we're going to do all the services and
then we're going to do all the API and
then we're going to do all the front end
and before you know it, you're on the
other side of,200 lines of code and it's
not working and now you have to go
figure out which part is broken because
there was no nothing really to test
along the way whether the model is
verifying it or whether you the human
are jumping in and checking it's
correct. And so what we've seen work
really really well across orgs of all
sizes um is what I call vertical plans.
This is how I build when I'm like before
AI I would like make a mock API endpoint
and then get it working in the front end
and then wire that and then mock out the
services layer and then do the database
migration and then put everything
together. And so even though it's the
same amount of code you have these like
checkpoints where you can see if it's
working and if it's not you can pause
and fix it before you go try to do the
rest of it. So these are just markdown
docs too. Like you can and should ask
for more detail. They start high level,
but like here's an example of like I
don't think you're going to get this
right. Tell me what you're thinking. And
it like dumped out the types and the
signatures.
Um and then getting better leverage from
the plan itself. I mean again like usual
like we've been doing. We just take that
artifact, we build it up with all the
previous artifacts and then we can go
build the plan. Um and it is the same if
you use create plan. It's the exact same
template, exact same setup, exact same
prompt, but this is a tactical doc for
the agent. we've already done enough
aligning that like I'm just going to
spot check this and then we save the
deep review for the actual code. And so
if you've used any of the RPI plans,
they look like this. It's the model
saying, "Hey, here's all the changes I'm
going to make." Um, the most important
part of this leverage is not just about
you and the agent, though. like human
agent alignment is important and knowing
what the agent's going to do and
correcting that is is good but it's also
you know if you're working with a team
of engineers we've found a lot of value
from taking these design discussions
these structure outlines and review I
said don't review the plans but these
shorter docs are really really good uh I
I am not the code owner of most of our
code at human layer my uh co-founder is
and I send him my design discussions on
purpose we don't have a required step
but I want to I want to know that when
we get code review, it's just going to
be like, "Yep, that's that's what I
wanted. That's it. That's it." So any
any of my bad decisions are headed off
on a 200line doc before I've gone and
written the code and gotten it working
and I'm attached to it. And so this is
really really powerful. Um before AI, we
would basically the way another way to
think about this is like time savings.
You would say, "Okay, it's a two-day
feature. I got to do all this stuff. The
coding is probably two to four hours."
If you just pick up cloud code and use
it to ship for you, you do get some
speed up because now the coding takes 20
minutes. It's still a two-day feature
because I still have to like align with
my team on what we're going to do. I
still have to get a code review and fix
stuff. Maybe I'm working across repos
that I don't personally own and then we
still have to verify and test it. But if
you use AI to help you with your
planning and alignment, then you also
save time there. And I think you get
much better alignment. Um, and so your
code review and rework is also much
shorter because you already know what's
coming. The team that's reviewing it
already kind of like had their chance to
re steer you. And really good teams do
this. It's they have a meeting that's
called architecture review where we
decide, you know, what's our technical
design doc on how we're going to build
this. So, um, as far as testing and
verifying, sorry, I don't have a good
answer for you. It's a whole other talk.
If you went to Drew's talk downstairs,
go find Drew Brun after this. He will
tell you all about testing and
verifying. Um, let's put this all
together. So, we have these five stages
of research and planning. Um, the
process is basically questions,
research, design, structure, outline,
plan, work tree, implement. Finally, the
poll request. Uh, that didn't make a
very good acronym though, so we just
picked the ones we liked. And, uh, we're
calling this crispy. Uh, so RPI to
crispy. That's the There you go. Um,
what's next and what did I not have time
to talk about today? Um, three steps was
already a lot for some people to learn
and now there are seven. I thought we
were supposed to make this easier for
teams to learn this and adopt it. we can
talk about how we're like thinking about
that. Um the idea of how do you measure
the impact of doing this um in
engineering teams I think is like we've
been trying to measure developer
productivity for 50 years and we still
don't know how to do it very well. Um
and then it's like if you're a central
kind of platform team rolling out
changes to everybody in your org, how do
you make these prompts better? How do
you make this engineering system better?
I mean, um, we were just talking about
like, oh, every team has a skill now,
and we want to consolidate and make that
shared and let people benefit from each
other's learnings. How do you make that
stuff better without like breaking
somebody's workflow or regressing it for
some some team? Uh, if you want to help
us, if you're in San Francisco and
you're working on critical systems and
you want to like figure out how to get
coding agents to do more, uh, let's
chat. We're also hiring. Um, send us a
note either way. Foundershumanlayer.dev.
Uh we're building a IDE that
orchestrates this stuff for you. Uh you
don't need this to get this value out of
this, but this is the kind of stuff
we're working on. Uh if you want to hang
out, I'm doing a sandbox research
hackathon on Saturday. We're going to
just get together with a bunch of cool
builders, test all of the sandbox
providers together, uh and see which
one's the best and then share our
learnings. I'll be also be at the
Daytona Compute Conference. Uh and if
you feel like coming to Miami, uh AI
engineer Miami is going to be really
fun. will be giving uh the updated
version of this talk with more stuff
that I didn't have time to get to today.
Um, thank you so much to all of you for
your energy to Demetrios and the entire
organizing squad. Good luck.
>> Questions. Who's got a question for Dex?
That was super fast. I like it. I was
very doubtful that you were going to get
through it, but I like
>> All right. I'm I'm curious about reading
the code. Like, it's not scalable,
right? Like, are we are you going to be
saying the same thing in six months? I
mean, six months ago, I said not to read
it. Uh, and it was I think everyone who
is saying don't read the code now is
going to be in six months being like,
"Yeah, we had to throw that out."
There's something there's something in
the middle, right? U, we're binary
searching through the space uh of how
much of the code should you read. Um, I
think, yeah, the idea is if you still
read the code, you can still get two to
threex speed up. And that's actually
better business outcomes than uh than
going 10x faster and shipping a bunch of
slop and hoping that you know GPT7 will
fix it for you.
>> Yeah, I hit things. Uh awesome talk. Um
curious your thoughts on like the
software factory. I think it's like
strong DM that's saying the opposite
which is like never have a human read
either side of it. And I think that
pushes us further into eval.
So what is your thinking on that?
>> Yeah, there is a whole class of like
there's a whole rabbit hole you can go
down with like formal verification and
TLA plus or I talked to a guy who's
building a new TA plus that is TA++ that
is like okay what if we don't read the
code? How can we actually like formally
verify everything that's working? Uh, I
think there's a lot more to be built and
I think there's a lot of people right
now who need to ship like code to
production systems faster. So like maybe
someday, but like I used to site Sean
Gro's talk where he was like it's just
the spec. Just write the document that
explains the desired behavior and you
treat the code like it's assembly and
you never read it anymore. Um,
I do not endorse that. Let's put it that
way.
>> We got one more. All right, last one.
Uh I know you mentioned one of the
slides about the like context window and
uh the the dumb zone, right? Uh I know
you researched that like heavily a few
like have have you like gone back to
look at that again to see how true that
still is after certain like context
window especially with like all the
autocompaction they have now and other
methods for that. I mean, I think like
>> for if you have been using AI coding
agents for six to nine months and you
use them for 60 hours a week, like the
dumb zone is not a useful concept to
you. I will regularly go up to 60. I
will regularly like aggressively keep it
below 30. It depends on the complexity
of your task, the amount of instructions
versus information. So like your mileage
may vary. If you are using coding agents
for the first time, this is what I this
is what we teach people is like if you
don't know what to do and you haven't
developed that intuition, then like
shoot to keep it under 40 and if you get
up to 60, like think about wrapping it
up and like you can keep iterating on
the same doc. That's what's also nice
about these is like we don't use the
built-in compaction because everything
that matters is going into static assets
and so you can always resume from where
you left off without having to worry
about the quality of an autocompact or a
manual compact.
>> Brilliant, Dex.
Well done, dude. Thank you. Let's give
it up for him. Huh? Yes.